Downloaded @ subs4free.club
"THEY SEEK THEIR MEAT FROM GOD"
- PSALMS 104:21
Where's it all begin?
Violence, the gun...
- Isabelle!
- ...the knife...
...the axe.
- Isabelle, come here.
- How's it born?
How's it start?
We all just wanna make it.
To live. To exist.
Stay out of the hoosegow.
We love if we're lucky.
We lose, we're damaged.
Hardened.
Isabelle.
We do what we have to.
What we are compelled to do.
Not true. I like Sidney
on account of his small prick...
...like a little mushroom.
Easiest coin I ever earned.
Barely even know it's in;
don't matter which hole.
- He's a disgusting little man.
- With a perfect little prick.
- Try not to talk so much like a whore.
- Try not to talk so much like a bitch.
- I got a bad itch this week.
- It's those fat railway fucks.
Dirtiest pricks in the entire county--
¡Hey!
OUTLAWS AND ANGELS
Wait! Please, no!
Grab the goddamn bag, goddammit!
Don't shoot!
C'mon, don't dillydally!
You! Get outta there, kid!
Samuel! Get up here
and thread this mark.
- What do you think?
- They pretty far shucked.
And I got these old eyes.
Sam, you slower than molasses
in January.
How the fuck these pricks
get the bulge on a lawman?
We was just making a deposit,
is all.
A deposit.
- I wasn't ready.
- Mayor Bishop is dead.
Goddammit!
Bled out real fast.
Fuck all.
Post the bounties,
then get Josiah on it.
Top coin.
I don't give a shit how much.
Just get it done.
Josiah?
They dragged him off somewhere.
No time to bury him.
Mayhap I should have the men
start peeking for the body?
Yeah, Have them round it up,
chop off the top.
If he sees fit, he can keep the coin.
I don't care.
We gotta keep heading south.
Don't wanna give them any time to breathe.
We slag any longer,
we're going to lose the track.
Boys, saddle up.
We ain't but a half day
behind 'em.
I ain't used my axe in a while...
...and I'd be lyin' if I said
I wasn't looking forward to it.
Charlie, what you playing at?
Bang, bang, bang!
- Look like hell, boy.
- Yeah, we're here, ain't we?
- The worst is comin' soon.
- Shut your yap.
Boys'll be fine.
Be prepared, is all.
Sure is good to see you, Aunt Esther.
You ain't aged a day.
I don't like it one bit what
you boys got yourselves into.
Shut your yap!
Don't listen to her, Charlie.
She don't know nothin'.
You better keep your hands
off that lady.
It's fine, boys.
I don't make no habit...
...but a woman needs discipline
at the proper time.
Just hand over the supplies,
we'll be on our way.
No need to bulldoze, son.
Me and Esther came
and done this on our own accord.
I didn't come nowhere
on nobody's own accord.
I think all y'all
be on-the-shoot.
All y'all gonna have to answer
to the Good Lord soon.
Shut your yap!
Now you listen here, old man.
- I'm big bug around here.
- No, no! Let him be!
You try that again, I'm gonna clean
your plow real good. You understand?
Henry, he can't breathe.
I'm fine, woman, I'm fine!
Well?
Hey!
You're gonna wanna go down
on the east side...
...through Rock Canyon...
...and White Sands.
Cross over outside of El Paso.
West trail's better. Through
Deming, cross in Columbus.
Ain't nothing on the east side
from here to the border. We'll dies.
Exactly.
Ain't nobody dumb enough
to track you that way.
Who says they're tracking?
There a bounty on your heads.
Eight thousand, all in.
- You're joshin'.
- I wish I was...
...for my nephew's sake,
but I ain't.
That man y'all shot, he died.
Government official.
Right and proper
from another county.
Bad luck!
He was a friend
of Sheriff McKay.
- They was compadres.
- Dammit all to hell!
I told you not to shoot that--
Hobble your lip, Charlie.
And that poor young woman, too.
We didn't kill no woman.
That's a lie.
You see how cruel you is?
You didn't even notice!
- Two-thousand each?
- Thousand on each of the boys.
The rest is on you.
They don't know us.
No way they could.
Tall man with the ivory grips
is what they call you.
And the... the fat man.
Who's the fat man?
Masks don't cover all it up.
If they don't catch you now,
you be alright.
They don't know your faces...
...but they gonna come at you hard,
especially you...
...until you're good and gone.
East trail it is.
Horses can't make it.
We can't carry enough water--
If they die, we'll foot it.
You can't foot
if you can't drink.
Well...
...let's hope that don't happen
till the final stretch.
Plenty of green patches
on the other side.
Fuck all, Henry!
Man,
you done fucked the rooster.
Dammit all to hell!
No...
Sorry, ma'am.
I truly am.
Goddammit, Henry...
...you can't shoot no woman.
Joe.
Joe! Joe!
Don't you do it...
...you fuckin' cow head.
My kin!
They's my goddamn kin!
You done crossed the line.
You know as well as I do...
...$8,000's enough to turn anyone.
Even kin, Henry. Even kin.
Alright, hand it to your sister.
- But I wanna do it again, Papa.
- Now, Charlotte, let's give a turn.
- Papa!
- Don't talk back to me, girl.
Here is.
Well! I'll be.
All you use good at
is boy things, you ugly rut.
Hush up.
I'll fetch more rounds.
You disgusting bitch.
You got clitchy chuck
all over my fingers.
Get up.
You alright, Button?
Alright, then.
Hey, now.
Never, ever point a gun
at somebody...
...unless you intend
to bed 'em down.
You bitch, I dare you.
Florence Ethel Tildon!
You put that gun down at once...
...or you're gonna get a whoopin'
like you've never had.
I was just kiddin', Daddy.
- Flo, you go to your daddy now.
- I'll go.
You best get in there,
give your daddy a rubdown...
...before supper unless
you want a whippin'.
- I'll go, Mama.
- Hush now, Charlotte.
- It's Flo's turn.
- But she got to--
No buts. You do as you're
told and shut it.
- Let her go, Mama. I don't want--
- No buts for you either, young lady!
Now git!
That's a good girl.
These bodies been out here
a lot longer than I like.
Josie.
There's something over yonder.
In the bushes.
Ahem.
Alright.
Whoever you be,
I implore you, reveal yourself.
We ain't gonna hurt you...
...long as you come out slow-like.
Last chance.
What's your name, little girl?
Don't be scared. C'mere.
All's good now.
What's your name?
Lulu.
Well...
...that's a pretty name.
Lulu.
What happened out here?
And who are you
to those folks?
My Grammy and Grampy
got shot good.
- Yeah. Who shot 'em, honey?
- I couldn't see them good...
...but I could hear them.
Bad men.
Yeah, bad men.
Now, do you know why the bad men
wanted to shoot your grandfolks?
Not sure.
I thought they were good
at first...
...and just getting Grampy
'cause he beat on us, but...
But what, honey?
But then they bed down Grammy.
And that ain't right.
I loved my Grammy.
When I heard them do that,
I sunk down in the brush.
I prayed Jesus
till they went away.
They did. But then the horses
run off and I was stuck.
I can ride.
If the horses was here,
I could've!
Now, I know this is
hard, Lulu, but...
I need to know
what those men said.
They said a lot of bad words
I shouldn't say.
No, not like that.
I need to know
where they went.
They said they was going
east, through White Sands.
- That's impossible.
- That's what they said!
I ain't lying!
No... that makes sense.
They know we'd have to be cracked
to follow 'em down these parts.
Well, I ain't cracked.
Ain't no coin worth that.
Goddamn.
What you get for talking
out your neck, yellow scamp.
Sorry, Lulu.
It's okay. He had it comin'.
Yeah. Now, we're gonna have
the yellow man...
...take the girl back to
town, we'll push on.
Boss...
...maybe we should think
about this.
I thought about it.
I think you oughta get
on your fucking horse...
...we'll go get some heads.
I'm starting to wonder if
we's dead and gone to hell.
Left rung...
firebug...
...snatch... wart.
You go and you get the pillow.
What the hell you yappin' about?
Build it! Build it strong
with the logger and the roots...
big John!
You okay, Maddie?
Probably too late to save myself
from the fire...
...but I'm gonna die tryin'.
Hallelujah and praise Jesus.
You mind your place.
I was just joshin'.
I wasn't.
Need some water, boys.
I'm hungry, goddammit.
Sun up, sundown
and back again with no eats.
- Steak'd be nice.
- Now he's joshin'.
Henry?
He gone.
Almost.
Whole side of his head's rotten.
Yeah, well,
better him than us.
I didn't mind him.
I'm not gonna talk ill
of the dead, but...
...I didn't care
for him much anyway.
You just spoke ill of a dead,
Charlie.
Shut the fuck up, Joe.
He's not quite dead yet,
but he's almost there.
Put him out?
Pfft! Waste of a good round,
if you ask me.
Well, that ain't nice at all.
Goddammit!
You happy now?!
I gots to have eats, Henry.
What we needs is some whores.
No eats and you might die.
If we die,
whores won't gonna matter.
- You're a smart one, kid.
- That's real funny.
Henry might as well dropped a
pile a shit in your mouth.
Shut your yap, Charlie.
I'll kills ya dead.
I'll make you a goner,
you dirty halfwit.
Hobble your lips.
Can't go much farther
without horses, Henry.
My foot's swole and these
bags is like lead.
Back.
Quiet!
Get down.
Well, I'll be.
That ain't no town, Henry.
Nope.
Town can't be too far.
Gotta get their congregation
somewhere.
They might have eats.
They'll have eats.
And they'll have horses.
Alright, boys.
We hit 'em at dark.
- Cackleberries?
- Yes, dear.
No, no. That'll do just fine.
- Charlotte?
- Yes, please.
Florence?
Can't handle
no more cackleberries.
Any more cackleberries
is the proper way, Florence.
I know, Mama,
but Daddy always says it.
Do as I say, not as I do, girl.
Yes, Papa.
You acts like you
all big and smart...
...but you can't even
says it right.
Leave me alone, sissy.
I'll leave you alone when I
want to, you dirty whore.
Hey, now!
Watch your language, young lady!
She should get a soap mouth
for saying that curse.
Only dumb ugly girls like you
get soap mouths.
Hey! Cut it out now!
One more word
and I will get the stick.
Please say grace, Georgie.
Come, Lord Jesus,
be our guest...
...and let these gifts to us
be blessed.
Amen.
Tastes real nice, Mama.
Well, thank you, honey.
Yep, mighty nice.
Are we gonna have milk
again soon?
Cow looks bony.
Can't figure if it's old age
or just not enough feed.
The good Lord
will always get us through.
Just testing us, that's all.
Yep, testing us good.
In all that plagues us in
this world, all the darkness...
...there will always a little God
to find.
And it's a beauty to behold.
Praise Jesus.
Hold on. Hold on now.
Stop eating right quick.
Mama, I'm hungry.
Can I please just finish--
Your mana's feelin'
the Holy Spirit now, Flo.
Ain't no way to plan
for when it comes.
Here it is.
"He causeth the grass
to grow for the cattle...
...and herb for the service of man...
...that he may bring forth
food out of the earth...
...and wine that maketh glad
the heart of men..."
Well, that's for some men...
...in the biblical times.
Not for you, Georgie.
- 'Course not.
- Nor for you girls.
I reckon that's stated proper,
'cause it says men, not women.
Women ain't allowed to
do nothing in that book.
Back in those times,
back in those times...
...drink was different.
Now it's the whiskey...
...got the devil in it.
The devil's work.
The devil's work is not right.
It's not right.
Sweetheart...
...don't get yourself
all worked up.
It's gotta stop.
Go on there,
read us the rest.
Yes, of course.
"Thou makest darkness,
and it is night...
...wherein all the beasts of
the forest do creep forth.
The young lions roar
after their prey...
...and seek their meat from God!"
They seek their meat...
...they seek their meat from He...
...God, Him.
Only He can bring us the grass
for the cow.
Only he can bring healing
to the town...
...and steady congregation
to us once again.
We do the work, but He decides.
You must always remember that.
Always, Mama.
Be thankful,
no matter how dark the time.
And worship.
- Praise Jesus.
- Praise Jesus!!
You may eat.
Go! Go!
Hoo!
Well, I'll be.
Dinnertime.
Back in your chair, ma'am.
Take a settle.
- Flo, get your hands up!
- No need for that, mister.
Y'all can put your hands down.
You heeled?
Just my scatter gun
over yonder.
There's another.
Under the bed in the sleep room.
Six-shooter.
Go on.
- Daddy, look what she did!
- They found it, they'd kill us.
It's okay, honey.
Smart young lady
you got there.
Now, mister...
Mister, I'm trying real hard...
...to be as nice
as I done well can.
Ain't gonna tell you
more than once.
Don't you ever lie to me.
Yes, sir.
That it?
Alright, then.
- He isn't gonna kill us?
- Hush now.
Can I ask what exactly
we can do for you boys?
You look like good boys.
Good Christians.
You wouldn't hurt us,
now would you?
I can assure you, ma'am, these
ain't good boys, I got here...
And I myself, well...
I's a hard case.
But we ain't here
to do no killin'.
I gots to have eats.
Yes, sir. We have...
...hens' eggs and...
bean sludge for you.
Nice and hot.
- I think we strike gold, Henry.
- If you're all finished...
...I'd ask you to slide yourselves
down yonder.
Get a wiggle on. Come on.
Keep your fire pointed
at their noggins, Joe!
- Where'd all that blood come from?
- Shut it now, girl!
Why's she trying to get us
all full of bullets?
Quit pokin' at 'em.
Nothin' wrong with the young lady
wanting to have some conversation.
She's just a dumb, stupid kid, sir.
Looks like a lady to me
if I ever seen one.
She's just stupid.
You're stupid.
Alright...
...let's be nice to each other
as we pass the time.
- I'm sorry, sissy.
- No, you ain't.
- Well, yes, I am.
Yes, she is already!
How many horses, mister?
Only two, sir,
and they's crow's bait.
Other two died
in the freeze-out.
Dammit! Dammit all to hell!
I got two pack mules, sir.
Mayhap that'll help.
I ain't ridin' no pack ass.
We'll take the horses...
...put Little Joe
on one of them mules.
Mighty slow movin'.
It'll get us to the meet-up.
Alright.
Listen here, mister.
We ain't gonna hurt you none
as long as you go along.
Alright?
We're gonna have a breath,
wash up...
...get some shuteye.
Then, at daylight, we're gonna
light a shuck outta here.
Well, what if the lawmen
comes tonight?
That's the smartest thing
he's ever said.
They wouldn't track us this far.
If they had the sand to do it,
they'd be tracking dead horses.
We got time.
You don't know that.
I don't care a continental what
you think I know or don't know.
What'd y'all do
to get in a fix like this?
What'd I tell you, girl?
It's their own, private
business, Flo.
I know what you're thinking,
mister.
- But we ain't like that.
- Like what?
We ain't killers.
We bank thieves.
We only beefed them 'cause
they was trying to beef us.
I knew we should've held off
when we saw who was in there.
- Rather be in a bone orchard?
- Might as well be.
More money on our noggins
than Jesse James.
Hobble that lip, Joe.
- We didn't hear nothin', sir.
- I'm sure you's good boys...
...who had to do
what you had to do.
How much? How much money
on your heads?
Keep it shut now!
Only way we're gonna kill you
is if you don't go along.
Liar.
You'll kill us either way.
That one there's
got a lip on her.
A mighty fine lip.
You sure got sand, lady.
Most cases...
...you'd be right.
But... we ain't up
for doin' that no more.
You ain't into doin' that
no more.
Unless need be, of course.
How you know
we won't squeal?
Because he knows we won't.
Right, sir?
We're gonna make
you flush, honey.
Rich people...
...they don't like to squeal.
That's mighty generous
of you, mighty generous.
We've never been flush before,
Daddy, have we?
No, honey. No, we haven't.
Make us lighter for the ride,
won't it, Charlie?
Sure will, big bug.
How far to the border?
Less than a day's ride.
Maybe a little longer,
draggin' plow.
Might be nice
to get roostered.
Please, Henry?
A few nips couldn't hurt.
You got any red eye?
There's some for medicinal
matters in the sleep room.
Alright.
What is it you called, ma'am?
Her name's Ada,
but that don't seem important.
Just be a good boy.
I know you's a good boy
who believes in Jesus.
I'll show you a good boy.
Come here, sit in my lap.
I will do no such thing.
You best not be making a mash
on no married woman loves Jesus.
I'm just having a little--
You ain't having nothing,
unless I say so.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
You should go for that one.
I'd rather die than to let you
put your filthy--
Shut it, gyp face. I'd rather die
than to put my filthy hands...
- ...on your pasty skin.
- Throw up the sponge, kid.
She laid into me first!
You ain't seen what I saw.
She been givin' me the eye
since we walked in.
Just tell me which one
I'm sticking it in.
Then I'll get right to it
soon as I'm done washing up.
You behave yourself
and be a good ol' boy, Joseph.
Need you to keep
outside watch tonight.
Mister, is the girl married?
No, I'm not.
But I don't have any interest
in boys or leavin' home.
She can't get
in the family way.
Fever got her when she's young.
Makes it hard.
I'm sorry to hear that.
But when I asked, I meant her.
- Her?!
- Yeah, her.
She hitched?
No, sir.
She's only 15.
Seems like she got some time.
Most boys in the town
with consumption.
What's your name, little bug?
We call her Florence.
Well, I'll be.
That's a sweet little name
for such a sweet little bug.
Please leave our girls
to themselves, sir.
We keep 'em pure and
in the path of Christ.
She a pretty lady.
I don't like
where this is going.
She ain't no lady.
She's just a girl.
Ain't any lady
is the proper way, Mama.
This ain't time for joking, Flo.
This man intends--
I intend to what, ma'am?
- Don't like what you're getting at.
- Don't mind my wife, sir.
She knows you don't
intend nothing sinister.
Why don't you hop up
on my lap now?
Now you wait a second there,
sir!
You leave my daughter be,
or you gonna have to fight me...
...like Kilkenny cats,
guns or no guns!
That's rich.
- Georgie! Christ in Heaven!
- Papa!
Papa! Papa!
Ain't gonna be no fight, mister.
- You ain't a good man.
- Never said I was.
- You're a curly wolf.
- Maybe.
You killed him!
He ain't dead.
He's just boogered up.
Now pony up, little bug.
I ain't gonna hurt you.
- Come on, missy.
- No! No, don't you touch her!
Hey!
No need for that, Charlie.
She was comin'
on her own legs.
Maybe I was, maybe I wasn't.
Still don't like
him pushing me places.
That's fair enough, bug.
Florence... Florence! No!
You best stay where you is.
Be a good boy
and make him stop...
...on account of Jesus!
Joe!
I don't know nothin'
about Jesus.
No need for that shit.
Sorry, Henry.
Alright now.
Gone on, little bug...
take yourself a nice nip.
He needs a doctor.
Broke nose don't need no doctor.
Keep that flannel mouth shut,
girl.
Everything's fine.
I... I don't need no doctor.
I'm just fine.
You see? Told you so.
He only hit me on account
of my threatening.
It's my own damn fault.
Now, that's the spirit, mister.
My apologies, ma'am.
No excuse for what he done.
I'm... alright.
You just as fine
as cream gravy.
You like sitting up here?
Like it better
if you didn't stink so darn bad.
Young lady's got a point.
I'll bet we smell worse
than pigs in shit.
I told you I need a wash.
My parts itches.
Where's the bathing happen
around here?
You boys get watered up.
We'll trade posts
when you're done cleanin'.
You wanna
get yourself washed up...
you best do it now.
Your family should pony up,
as well.
They'd like to water up now,
that's their concern.
What in Jesus's name
does she think she doing?
That's a smart girl.
It's a mighty fine, what she's layin' out.
Don't you reckon?
Reckon what?
She's trying
to save our lives.
If you told
I'd gotten a chill...
...six marks on a clock ago,
I'd have laughed you down.
Wind's coming at night,
beast-like...
...this time of the year.
Fire feels nice.
What's your trade, mister?
Mr. Tildon preaches
the Good Lord's word.
In that little church house?
Yes, sir. When it's full.
We gonna run into any funny
business in the morning?
People walking about?
No, sir. Town's a few miles in.
We ain't had...
...nobody at morning service, or
any other, for months now.
Like I says,
town's got the consumption...
...everyone's shut in.
I'm gonna get some shuteye...
...get myself a nice rubdown.
I'm sore deep.
You know how, little bug?
Sir, may I say my piece?
Much obliged.
I wanted to plead with you
one last time, man to man...
...please leave my little Flo's
purity for her husband...
...whomever that may be.
- Please just be a good boy.
- I ain't no boy.
Let me handle this.
Your daughters give you
rubdowns, I take it.
Why, yes, sir.
That's the frontier way.
Daddy likes it when I do it best,
'cause my hands are strong.
Yes, yes, honey.
Just... quiet down.
All I want's a rubdown,
same as you.
Nothing sinister.
Nothing...
...sexual.
This is a house of God.
We don't talk about such things.
What kind of things?
Sexual things?
Joe, you keep outside watch
tonight.
Take the other girl with you.
Daddy? Daddy!
Stop him, Daddy!
He'll behave himself.
Charlotte, Charlotte,
you just go along.
Everything'll be fine.
I'll try.
Honey. H-honey, look at me.
I love you.
I love you, Daddy.
Joe, you behave yourself.
No funny business.
Pony up, little bug.
First light, we move.
We're lucky
if they ain't dead.
They didn't find no horses.
You have to prepare for
a stretch like that to make it.
Well, maybe they was prepared.
I doubt it.
They're bank robbers,
not trackers.
I doubt it, too, but...
...they're gonna come across
some horses soon.
And if they're still kicking,
they might kill for 'em.
I don't think it's smart,
us going in only two like this.
With surprise,
we'll get the bulge on 'em.
When we get to Mesilla...
...I plan to picking up
some more muscle.
That'll help.
Honest, I don't miss the boys.
Their water's been more use
than them crossing this stretch.
Yeah.
Get up.
Alright...
...C'mon.
You have the oils?
We use chicken fat.
We'll do it dry.
Well, now take it up.
Get positioned proper, honey.
Shit.
What the dickens got into you,
little bug?
I'm sorry.
Sonofabitch.
I should've asked.
Girl...
...even I'm...
...belly fired...
...I ain't partial to that.
I'm sorry.
Shit.
What are you doin'?
What's wrong?
Am I not doin' it proper?
I ain't opposed to relations
with you.
As a matter of fact...
...I have a fire in my belly
right now.
But this ain't the way
I want it.
I wanna bed you proper.
But you're acting more like...
...an adventuress than a lady.
You been with one of them?
Been with a couple in my day,
I reckon.
But you gotta remember, I'm old.
You're not old.
For a lawbreaker...
...I'm ancient.
What was it like
with the painted ladies?
Did they do it good?
They have their own way.
But if I wanted
those kind of relations...
...I could have 'em
any time I want.
Now, what got into you,
little bug...
...make you do
a thing like that?
Youse likes to talks
about anything?
Alright.
Youse real lucky
Henry called me off...
...or I'd be fucking you silly
right now.
Where'd that come from?
Knife.
Where'd those come from?
I think you know.
I suppose I do.
Did it hurt?
Every time.
Better than not hurting, though.
That means it's all over.
I never met a man like you.
I reckon you ain't met many men.
Not many, but some.
I thought they were all
like my daddy.
I was wrong.
You are a good man.
I ain't never been accused
of such.
Well, I'm accusing you.
How's your riding legs?
Better than most girls...
...worse than most boys, I suppose.
- That'll do.
- I'm tough enough.
You ever been down Mexico way?
No.
Mighty pretty
in the right spots.
Henry?
Yes, darlin'.
You fancy me?
I reckon I do.
I fancied you soon the moment
you walked through that door...
...even though I knew I shouldn't.
But it's different now.
Now that I know
you're a good man.
Henry?
Yes, darlin'.
I never been kissed before.
Damn near Apache country.
Maybe they got 'em already.
Maybe.
I doubt it, though.
That stretch would've got 'em
before the Apache did.
I just wanna collect 'em.
I don't care if they're
dead already or alive...
...as June Wiggles,
I just wanna collect 'em.
Josiah.
It's okay to lose out once.
Hell, we're done flush already.
Nobody's gonna hold
it against us.
No, it ain't,
and that ain't what it's about.
You oughta think about shutting
your cock-holster,
'less you wind up like old
yellow man over there.
You back down, Josiah.
I'm not one of your whores.
I won't quit until you do.
I'm just saying.
Yeah, just sayin'.
Let's light a shuck. Come on.
Take a sit on your seat.
Alright now.
We all clear?
We's good.
Time to hightail it.
I knew that bastard'd keep
the woman the whole damn night.
If my knob was slimy
with done cunny...
...I'd have stayed in there too.
Wake it up now, Henry.
Time to light a shuck!
Dammit, come on.
Already late.
Don't wanna tempt fate.
Them's rhymin' words, Charlie!
Well, ain't you smart.
Take a settle...
...knuckleheads.
What the fuck is this?
What do you think?
Who's she think she is,
Calamity Jane?
Well...
...this here's the new member
of our gang.
What's gotten into you, sissy?
You got rocks in your noggin,
Henry?
- I'd mind your tone.
- I'll mind my tone just fine...
...but I'm mighty worried about
you givin' fire to this girl.
- You don't know about her.
- I'd mind your tone more.
- That's my wife-to-be.
- Wife-to-be?
Ain't nobody
gonna say nothing?
Ain't nothing nobody can say,
missy.
First church crossing the border
we're gonna do it proper...
...ain't we now, Henry?
Why, yes, we is, little bug.
That way, I'm keeping
my promise, old man.
- Save her for her husband.
- Charlotte...
No, no, honey,
I done got my nose boogered...
...but my legs are just fine.
Flo, you're upsetting your mama.
Why don't you come on
back to earth now?
I'm already right here
on earth, Papa.
Henry and I
are going off together.
Please, sir. I beg you.
In the name of the Good Christ.
She's just a baby.
She don't know what she's doin'.
Now I can tell...
...that you are a good man.
Just like your husband?
Yes, sir.
Now, I know you don't wanna
lead her to the fire...
...when she's just a young'un.
She deserves a chance
to lead a righteous life.
You shut it, Mama.
I've had about enough of you.
Honey, I love you.
You're my little baby!
Honey, my sweetest,
darling little girl.
I know you're just making a mash
to save us...
...but this here's a fair man.
He got no need to bed us down.
He would've done it already.
Henry, we gots to cut stick.
Flo...
...you just tell this man...
...that you love your family
and that we need you.
You tell him you can't go.
- Yes.
- I see here a man that...
...he wants to make his way
away from the fire.
I see a man th-that wants
to lead the righteous way.
- Yes.
- I see a man here that might--
Sissy, why you playing
such devilish games?
I ain't playin'.
Well, hell!
Ain't she a firecracker.
Honey... why you wanna
point a gun at your daddy?
What I ought to do
is open a crater in your face...
...with this here pistol.
What you think about that, Papa?
Well...
...it sounds to me
like he done bamboozled you...
- ...turned you against your own pa--
- Sissy, that's just about enough!
Now, you leave Daddy alone!
Be a good girl, honey,
put the gun down.
Just remember that the
good Lord is testing us.
We can still serve him, honey,
and make everything better.
Honey, we got
to stick together as family.
- Yes.
- Alright.
That's enough.
You wanna do this right, sweets.
Siddown.
Fresh?
Hold on.
We got 'em alright.
They're on foot, headed to
Mesilla, and this boy here...
...he's bleeding
like a wag tail on the rag.
I wouldn't be surprised
if we come up on another stiff.
Which way?
Well, from here in...
...there's only one way
that men can trek.
By the looks of this...
...they ain't but two hops
and a holler away.
Do we ride?
Hell, yes. Let's cut stick.
- Can I sit with my family, sir?
- I ain't gonna tell you twice.
Sit... down.
You too, missy,
other side of the table.
Henry, what the hell's
going on here?
- We need to cut stick.
- It'll just take a few minutes.
But it ain't arguable.
Best grab a chair.
What in the Good Christ's name
is being got at here?
You shut your fucking mouth
till I tell you different!
Hey, bug...
...the things we talked about,
what do you wanna do first?
First thing...
or the second thing?
The second thing.
Alright, then.
Makes sense.
Have at it.
No!
No!!!
Siddown!!
She ain't fucking around.
No, she ain't!
Charlotte!!
I'm sorry, sissy.
I meant to hit you up higher.
Move it, Mama.
'Less you wanna get sprayed.
Bug.
We're all damned
to eternal burning.
All of us, all of us.
All damned.
And the devil that deceived
was thrown...
...into the lake of fire and
brimstone, where the beast...
Shut up, woman!
To the lake of fire and brimstone...
- Take a settle now, woman!
- Shut your fucking yammer box.
Shut!
God!!
What you've done
is unforgivable!
The devil's in you now!
There ain't nothing can keep
your soul outta the fires.
Ain't nothing more demonic
than striking down...
...your own flesh and blood,
your own kin!
Shut it, mister.
I'd like to exchange words now,
man to man.
Take off your vest.
- P-pardon?
- You do as you're told.
Take off your vest.
Get that outta here, will ya?
Backdoor.
You look at me
when I talk to you.
Yes, sir. I'm ready to talk.
Now don't be a lickfinger.
I wasn't licking no finger... sir.
Why don't you tell me...
...how your oldest daughter
got all twisted up inside.
Why she couldn't be
in the family way.
I told you that already.
She got the fever.
You sure about that?
Yeah, 'course I'm sure.
Now...
...you have two choices,
you sonofabitch.
Humiliation or death.
Now, you either speak truth...
...or I'll pull the trigger.
Well?!
She was pregnant.
What?!
- She was in the family way.
- When?!
When was she in the family way?!
- Please, sir, don't make me--
- You say it!
I was sick... I was sick
with the devil's seed!
I was sick with the drink!
- There was a demon living here with us!
- How old?!
A demon!
God have mercy on us all.
How old was she, mister?
Eleven.
Eleven... years old.
And I speak the truth when...
...when I say digging that baby
out of her...
...is what twisted her
all up inside?
You look at me.
Who put her in the family way?
Who planted that filthy seed?
That was the devil's work.
That was the drink.
You... you frontier folk is wrong,
if there ever was such a word.
- The devil's work? The drink?
- Yes, sir. Yes, sir!
And I guess that you...
...you just... done fixed that, right?
- Yes, sir.
- Yeah? Long time ago?
Yes, sir. I...
We... we brought
Christ back into our home.
I quit the drink.
We drove the demon out.
So now the demon's clean gone?
And you repent?
So all's good? Good with God?
Yes, sir. Christ forgives.
He forgives.
Yes, he does, mister...
Yes, he does!
So I have one more question.
If the... the devil...
...if he's gone from this house...
...well, then, that must've been you...
...getting your dirty ass licked...
...and your tiny prick slopped on...
...by my bride-to-be last week...
...and the week before that
and the week before that!
Hey, you shush!
I might just pump you
full of lead...
...on account of you knowin'
it was goin' on all these years.
Yeah, that's right.
You see...
Here's the thing.
...Christ forgives.
He does.
But I don't.
Hey!
Joe.
- Yes, sir.
- Here you are, old boy.
I need you to do something
for me.
I need you to fuck this man proper
right there in that shit hole.
- What did you fuckin say? - Please don't!
- Keep your heads down!
- What did you fuckin' say?
Charlie, you mind the ladies
for me, will ya?
Take 'em outside a spell.
My pleasure.
I don't need to put eyes
on this sick shit.
I don't know about this, boss.
I ain't never done
nothin' like it.
You'll be fine as cream gravy.
Now whip out that knob, boy.
Hey!!
You so much as move
another muscle...
...I'm gonna put two bullets
in the back of your head...
...before you can say
eat my asshole.
- Okay.
- Where's that chicken fat?
Heh! We're all out!
Shame.
Looks like Joe's going in dry.
I don't like some man ass.
You put it in the back
of a woman, I reckon.
Yes, sir, once or twice...
...with the old ladies
at Miss Rita's.
There you go. Alright.
Now you just close your eyes
and you imagine it's that...
...nice lady's ass.
Well, alright,
I reckons I can do that.
Alright, then.
You stay right there.
Hey, mister.
You ready?
No!
Alright, go.
Now you hit him nice and hard.
Make sure he knows it's in him.
I ain't worked up, Henry.
I gots to get it ready.
Alright. That's fine.
And you... take your time.
You stay comfortable.
You shush.
You know...
...usually I'd wait till after.
But this is too good.
Ain't I the matchmaker?
All set. It's ready, Henry.
Alright, old boy...
...now you shove it in there
nice and deep.
No!! Please! Please!
Just shoot me! Please!
Please! Shoot me!
...Stop! Stop.
Joe, stop.
You done good, boy.
I don't gotta gets it in, Henry?
No. No, you don't.
I just wanted to scare him,
is all.
Now put that thing back
in your riding pants.
Thank you!
Thank you from the bottom
of my gullet!
Hey, Joe...
...fetch Florence.
And you...
...get your ass up off the table
and sit down.
You not gonna kill me?
Thank you, sir!
Thank you. Thank you.
You'r welcome.
I'm gonna clean the devil out...
proper this time.
- How you doin', little bug?
- ¡Properly!
You think about what you wanna use?
Alright, then.
I reckon this'll do.
She gonna shoot me?
No, no, no, Nancy pants.
You see...
she wanted to at first.
Then I told her, y'know,
gunshot's quick, it's easy.
Gunshot's a good death.
You deserve to feel it.
Holy hell, girl!
You still have doubts
about our new member?
Hell no!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You okay, honey?
You alright?
Water.
Hey, Joe, grab some water,
will you?
Alright?
I'm sorry.
For a woman, little bug...
...you done mighty fine.
Thanks, Joe.
I never seen
anything like that.
I suppose the look of it just...
turned my stomach.
It's normal.
You done real good. Real good.
No. No.
I wanna finish it.
Ma'am...
...can I indulge?
Alright.
Now, don't take this
the wrong way...
...but there are better ways
to finish.
Now, you cracked him
mighty hard, but...
...he's still alive.
I thought he'd be dead
after I broke his eye like that.
Yeah, you'd think so?
But it don't always work
that easy.
You gotta hit
in the proper place.
Now...
do you want to finish him now...
...or you wanna make him suffer
a little bit more?
Not much more.
Alrighty.
Lookie here.
You hit him here,
he dies immediate-like.
You hits him right here,
right here...
...just make him squeal like a pig.
A thousand thanks, sir.
Call me Charlie.
We're friends now.
Finish him, darlin'.
Now that's a show
if I ever seens one.
Quiet, old boy.
Alright.
Let's get you cleaned up.
Missy?
Yes, Charlie?
Why'd you bed down your sis?
She liked it.
Violence...
...how does it all begin?
The violence.
We're either on one side of it
or the other.
Sometimes both.
Where's the innocence go?
Is it gone?
Or is it always there
beneath the darkness?
Trying to remind us
who we are.
How do we lose ourselves?
Or we find in our true selves?
The innocence or the darkness?
Which are we?
You got some blood
on your face.
I'm leaving, Mama.
I was gonna kill you.
- Why...?
- Stubborn.
Why would you kill...?
Shut your yap, I beg.
I was going to kill you,
but Henry convinced me not to.
He said he didn't wanna
spill no more blood...
...didn't want me
getting too used to it.
Now, I reckon there gonna be
bounty-hunters and lawmen...
...on account of that big reward
they're offering.
You best keep your mouth shut,
Mama.
Remember,
this is a gift Henry gave you.
The gift of life.
And also best remember...
...that you will not know
where I am...
...and I will know where you are.
You understand?
Yes.
Henry told me
to leave you that.
I wish I...
I would wish...
I know, Mama.
Those boys fucked a rooster.
It's a mess.
Let's take a look-see
around the property.
I need you
to tell me everything.
Where'd they go?
Woman!
Well... that's that.
Did you wanna make a run?
You know I'm with you.
The border's close
and they hours ahead of us.
We're beat.
We're not beat.
They just got our goat,
just once.
It's up to you. You're the boss.
We could stay.
Or we could cross over
and we could look for 'em.
No, I think you oughta
get on back to your family.
I'm gonna poke around
Mesilla a little bit...
...get a hot bath, you know,
kinda linger, see if I can't--
Hey, hey, I'll stay.
I know you will.
I'm well-upped, though.
You cut on out,
get back to your family.
You're the boss.
At least we got two of them...
Yeah, we did.
Sometimes we decide
to take the wrong path.
We think we're righteous.
Surprise ourselves.
We go toward the fire.
Make the wrong choice.
And we're beat.
It's all over.
Open your eyes, little bug.
Mexico.
You and me.
- You and me.
- C'mon, love birds!
Let's get a wiggle on!
We cross, then we rest easy!
I'll never be able to show you
how grateful I am.
You will.
And I will.
Got all the time in the world.
No.
Henry!!
Henry?
I'm sorry, Henry.
I wanted to, I really did.
I just couldn't.
That reward money
is good, clean coin.
Well...
...that's it.
Didn't Daddy ever tell you
about revolvers?
You always, no matter what...
...gotta leave one chamber empty.
You know why?
It's 'cause if you're addle-handed...
...and you stack up all six
and the gun drops, bam!
Then you've got yourself
in a real bad box.
Hell, Henry told me...
...he once knew a man
who shot off his own ball.
Never could have relations
again.
Poor thing.
Are you alright, Mother?
You look balled up.
I know.
I reckon today's
been a bag of nails.
Lots of changes.
OUTLAWS AND ANGELS
Resynced by
jantoniot
In memory of
FRANK GIFFORD
Dedicated to ROSS "PAPA" PALLONE,
The Italian Cowboy.
There was never a western he didn't see...
Ahem.
Mighty nice, Joe.
Mighty nice.